## KHUSHBOO GUPTA

Unity Programmer khushboofromindia@gmail.com

Phone No: -9871330054

India

#### LINKS

Portfolio

https://khushboogupta17.tech/

Github

https://github.com/khushboogupta17

Linkedin

https://linkedin.in/in/Khushboogupta17

#### **SKILLS**

Unity2d, Unity3D, C#, Github, ARcore, ARFoundation, firebase, SQL, C++, Shadergraph, Photoshop, Illustrator, Blender

#### **EDUCATION**

Computer Science BTECH (June 2017-June 2021) CGPA-9.02

### **COURSES**

**1.** Introduction to Game Developemnt by Michigan State University

May 2020 -July 2020

- **2.** C# Survival Guide on Unity Learn August 2020 -December 2020
- **3.** Multiplayer FPS by Brackeys(backed by Unity)

April 2018-May 2018

**4.** Tower Defence by Brackeys(backed by Unity)

May 2018-July 2018

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced game Programmer having tried hands in 2D ,3D and AR games. I have worked on advance C# concepts like scriptable objects, delegates and design patterns. I have knowledge of various data structures and have implemented dialogue systems, puzzle creation from environment and runtime mesh generation system.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 1. ViDoor (Personal Project)

December 2019-December 2020

An AR indoor navigation app implementing concept of graphs and shortest route from source to destination. It was a team project where I led the team and created the runtime graph creation functionality and storing it in firebase for future access.

#### 2. Don't Lose... (Personal Project)

(October 2019 – December 2020)

AR message driven puzzle game where player gets locked outside his house and someone trapped inside ,guides him to enter into the house through clues. I worked on Animator Controller extensively for animations and created puzzles from environment. Here You can watch the little clipping <a href="here">here</a>

# 3. Snowy Laws(Internship at Stellenar Pvt Ltd.)

June 2019-August 2019
2D side scroller moh

2D side scroller mobile game having both endless mode and challenge mode with simple controls like jump and slide. Here I implemented Object Pool design pattern to randomly generate obstacle at fix intervals .Uploaded on <u>playstore</u>.

## 4. Color Pencil (Internship at Intellisense Pvt Ltd.)

*March 2019 – April 2019* 

It is Level mode and endless mode 2D mobile game Inspired by Color Snakes by ketchapp, build complete game in a month in the guidance of a mentor. Here I implemented Object Pool design pattern to randomly generate obstacle of different color .Have a look here.

# 5. Spherothon (Internship at International Organization of software developers)

Dec 2018 – Jan 2019

Spherothon is a 3D mobile casual game available at google playstore. It has simple controls of right and left swipe to cross the levels. A game with a simple theme keeps on getting challenging after every three levels. Uploaded on <u>playstore</u>.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- **1.** 2<sup>nd</sup> runner up position at Unite India hackathon'19 from 400+ entries
- 2. Won 5+ Hackathons with more than 200 entries
- 3. Awarded Grace Hopper Celebration India student scholarship 2020
- **4.** Game development mentor at IOSD BPIT
- 5. Impacted 100+ students in unity Game Development
- **6.** Led a team of 15 people
- 7. Designing student assistant at Teach India for 1 year